ALEJANDRO GONZÁLEZ

me@algorodev.com · 648183931 Valencia, Spain · 9 June, 1997

Tech-enthusiast with +4 years of experience as a programmer. Quick adaptation to new challenges and responsibilities. Experience of working with tight deadlines and under time pressure while ensuring quality. Great interest in acquiring and improving skills. Experience working with agile methodologies.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2022 - NOW

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, INFOSER (MERCEDES-BENZ)

Analyze, document and develop new features of a big data application using NodeJS, Express, PostgreSQL, Typescript, React and Material Design.

Using Jest, Supertest and Playwright for unit, integration and e2e testing.

Using SonarQube as code quality analyzer.

Using GitHub as repository where we performed project CI/CD.

Using Jira as task manager.

OCT 2021 - SEP 2022

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, CAPGEMINI (CAPGEMINI)

Analyze, document and develop the folder structure and code of a budget calculator application using Nest, PostgreSQL, TypeORM, Typescript, Angular, Sass, Material Design and NgRx.

Analyze, document and develop the folder structure and code of a sustainability application using Typescript, Angular, Sass, Material Design and NgRx.

Analyze, document and develop the folder structure and code of a dashboard application using Nest, PostgreSQL, Prisma, Typescript, Angular, Sass, Material Design and NgRx.

Using Nx to manage the monorepo.

Using StoryBook for component documentation.

Using Jest, Supertest and Cypess for unit, integration and e2e testing.

Using SonarQube as code quality analyzer.

Using AWS as repository where we performed project CI/CD.

Using Jira as task manager.

MAR 2021 - OCT 2021

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, INCRENTA

Analyze, document and develop of the application previously developed in HTML, CSS and Laravel, to React with Typescript, Sass and Bootstrap.

Using GitLab as repository where we performed project CI/CD.

Using Jira as task manager.

Using SonarQube as code quality analyzer.

SEP 2020 - MAR 2021

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, VINFOVAL

Analyze, document and develop new features using Angular, Sass, Bootstrap, DevExtreme and SmartAdmin.

Using Azure as a repository where we performed project CI/CD, and as task manager too. Using SonarQube as code quality analyzer.

JUN 2019 - JUL 2022

FREELANCE

Analyze, document and develop the architecture, folder structure, design and code of an E-Commerce using NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, React and Typescript.

Analyze, document and develop the architecture, folder structure, design and code of an E-Commerce using NodeJS, Express, MongoDB and Angular.

Analyze, document and develop the architecture, folder structure, design and code of an online Academy using NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, Angular and Typescript.

Using Bitbucket as a repository where I performed project CI/CD, and Jira as a task manager. Using Jest, Supertest and Cypess for unit, integration and e2e testing.

Using SonarQube as code quality analyzer.

EDUCATION

JUN 2020

BOOTCAMP FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, GEEKSHUB ACADEMY

Learn about HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, SQL, MongoDB, Angular, React, Wordpress, PHP, Laravel, Git, Github, JQuery, Bootstrap, Material Design, Redux, Mongoose, Express, Sequelize, Docker.

Develop a web application using Angular, NodeJS, Express and MongoDB.

Develop a web application using React, NodeJs, Express and MongoDB.

Using GitHub as repository.

Using Docker to create containers of our applications.

JUN 2019

TÉCNICO SUPERIOR EN DESARROLLO DE APLICACIONES MULTIPLATAFORMA,

CIEEP PROGRESA

Learn about Java, Javascript, Angular, NodeJS, Android, Swift, MySQL, MatisseSQL, MongoDB, HTML and CSS.

Develop a console application using Java.

Develop a mobile application using Android, HTML, CSS and MySQL.

Develop a mobile application using Swift, HTML, CSS and MongoDB.

Develop a web application using Javascript, HTML, CSS.

Develop a web application using Angular, NodeJS, MongoDB, HTML and CSS.

JUN 2017

TÉCNICO EN SISTEMAS MICRO INFORMÁTICOS Y REDES, CIEEP PROGRESA

Learn about systems, networks, hardware, software and servers.

Assemble a computer per parts.

Build a VPN.

Install and work with a clean SO.

CERTIFICATION

NOV 2016

CAMBRIDGE B1

DEC 2021 – DEC 2023

SAFE 5 PRACTITIONER CERTIFICATION